So I came to support Palestine really started in 2021 when there was the annual attack on the Al-Aqsa Mosque.
And that particular year, it was just excessive on another level.
And I think also because we were all inside, we were still in COVID mode.
There was just a lot more social media interaction.
And because of BLM and my commentary on BLM, I think I was algorithmically put in some different spaces than I had been before.
And so when this happened, there started to be a lot of Palestinian folks reaching out to me saying, like, why aren't you talking about this?
Why aren't you talking about this?
And I had suffered under the Hasbara of, well, it's too complicated, you know, and not wanting to offend.
And, you know, that's just like me being like a genuine, considerate person.
Like, I just don't want to step into spaces where I don't know the knowledge.
But everyone was like, you need to talk us!
And I was like, okay, my stepmother is Palestinian.
I'm not, like, close with my stepmother.
But I said, let me, like, ask my sister.
And then, of course, Dr. Mark Lamont Hill is one of my really good friends.
And he was blacklisted for speaking, for literally just saying from the river to the sea at the UN.